<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mo="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/mac/office/2008/main" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:mv="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:mac:vml" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:b/><w:sz w:val="32"/></w:rPr><w:t>Ethics-Constrained Economic Mechanisms on Tau Net:</w:t><w:br/><w:t>The Alignment Theorem and the Virtuous Cycle Compounder</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Dana Edwards (DarkLightX)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>December 2025</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p/><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Abstract</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>We propose an incentive architecture for Tau Net in which a continuously updated ethical consensus signal directly scales on-chain rewards. Users publish machine-checkable ethical models; an aggregation layer computes a bounded Ethical–Economic Transaction Factor (EETF) E(t) that represents the current consensus; and alignment-aware agents (exemplified by the Virtuous Cycle Compounder, VCC) optimise against E(t) under deflationary scarcity. We formalise the ethics-to-incentives pipeline, state an alignment theorem showing that increasing scarcity makes misalignment eventually suboptimal even in the presence of bounded external gains from unethical behaviour, and describe a Lean 4 mechanisation that ties the result to enforceable type-level invariants. Finally, we connect the proof to executable Tau specifications and trace-based analytics used to test VCC agents.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:rPr><w:b/></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Keywords: </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:t>Tau Net; incentives; ethics aggregation; formal verification; Lean; deflationary token economics</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>1. Introduction</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>In decentralised economic systems, incentive design is the practical interface between values and behaviour. Static rule sets and off-chain governance are often too slow to track changing community norms, and they offer limited guarantees when autonomous agents exploit reward gradients. Tau Net’s design suggests an alternative: treat ethics as a first-class, machine-readable object and convert the aggregated ethical consensus into an explicit input to on-chain economics.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>This paper advances three contributions. (i) We specify an ethics aggregation pipeline that maps on-chain ethical models into a bounded scalar EETF signal E(t) used by economic agents (Fig. 1). (ii) We formalise a reward model for alignment-aware agents, then prove an Alignment Theorem: under sustained deflationary scarcity and an eventually positive EETF, rational agents that maximise expected payoff switch to an ethical regime after a finite threshold and remain there. (iii) We connect the proof to implementation: a Lean 4 development that encodes range/positivity constraints in types, and Tau agents (including the VCC family) whose traces can be analysed against the same invariants.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2. Background</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.1 Tau Language and knowledge representation</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Tau Language is an executable formal specification framework aimed at program synthesis and verifiable smart contracts. In the present context, its key role is to represent user-contributed ethical models as logical theories and to support sound updates of those theories over time. Users broadcast models into a shared knowledge graph where they can be compared, refined, audited, and (critically) aggregated into a consensus signal consumed by economic agents.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.2 Ethics aggregation and the EETF signal</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Let M = {m_i}_{i=1..N} be the set of published ethical models. An aggregation operator A combines these models into a bounded real-valued signal E(t) = A(M, t) ∈ [0, 3] at discrete time t (e.g., epoch or block height). E(t) is interpreted as the Ethical–Economic Transaction Factor (EETF): higher values represent stronger consensus support for the behaviours encoded by the aggregated models.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>A practical aggregator must provide: (a) validity screening (exclude inconsistent or demonstrably malicious models), (b) resistance to small coalitions attempting to skew E(t), and (c) liveness (E(t) updates as models are added or revised). The Alignment Theorem stated below depends only on boundedness and eventual positivity of E(t); the concrete choice of A determines robustness properties and is therefore part of the system’s security model.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.3 Virtuous Cycle Compounder (VCC)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The Virtuous Cycle Compounder is a family of alignment-aware agents that consumes E(t) and implements three mechanisms (Fig. 2): Dynamic Base Reward (DBR), Hyper-Compounding Rewards (HCR), and Aggressive Ethical Burn (AEB). DBR scales baseline rewards with alignment; HCR increases rewards for sustained alignment over time; and AEB retires supply whenever collective ethics stay high, treating burns as gratitude for virtuous flows rather than as punitive withdrawals.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.4 Verification and visualization stack</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The ethics signal, theorem, and implementation artifacts are cross-checked along three axes. First, a Lean 4 development proves the Alignment Theorem without unproven axioms, ensuring the scarcity-threshold argument is machine checked. Second, Tau agents (v35–v54 plus shared libraries) run both in the native interpreter and in an exact Python simulator so finite-state traces satisfy the same invariants. Third, stakeholder-facing visualisations-including the standalone Alignment Theorem dashboard and the VCC concept explorer-show how shifts in E(t) ripple through DBR/HCR/AEB in real time, making the incentive surface auditable.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.5 Tau testnet substrate and extralogical primitives</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The tau-testnet reference implementation treats Tau specifications as first-class chain data: every revision transaction is replayed pointwise so only the targeted formulas change, and validation logic re-applies the Tau engine before admitting rule edits to the mempool. The runtime also exposes an extralogical API for BLS verification, commit-reveal flows, networking, and storage, giving DBR/HCR/AEB contracts a trustworthy way to call crypto and IO from within Tau rules while keeping the logical kernel minimal. Preference aggregation specs can therefore implement utilitarian or ranked-choice logic: users express utilities as logical statements, commit and reveal them for fairness, and the aggregation layer merges the revealed values into the consensus EETF signal.</w:t></w:r></w:p></w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>2.6 Preference-utilitarian aggregation</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Because Tau specs are ordinary logic, we can encode Harsanyi-style preference utilitarianism: agents post preference formulas or utility terms, Tau enforces comparability and affine scaling, and the aggregation spec sums or averages utilities subject to Pareto constraints. Commit-reveal keeps submissions private until everyone has committed, and the resulting utilitarian or ranked-choice operator runs entirely on-chain, making every assumption about weights, normalization, or distance metrics auditable.</w:t></w:r></w:p></w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>3. Formal model</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>3.1 Supply, deflation, and scarcity</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Let S(t) &gt; 0 denote normalised token supply at discrete time t ∈ ℕ with S(0) = S0. Deflation is modelled as</w:t><w:br/><w:t xml:space="preserve">    S(t+1) = S(t) · (1 − r(t)),</w:t><w:br/><w:t>where r(t) ∈ [r_min, r_max] ⊂ (0, 1). Define scarcity as M(t) = S0 / S(t). Under sustained deflation with r_min &gt; 0, M(t) is monotone non-decreasing and diverges to +∞. Infinite divisibility is an engineering assumption that preserves usability as S(t) becomes small by exposing finer subunits.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>3.2 Economic pressure</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>We define economic pressure as P(t) = M(t) · E(t). This combines scarcity and consensus: when a scarce unit is also strongly coupled to an ethical signal, the opportunity cost of deviating from the consensus can dominate other bounded payoffs.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>3.3 Agent payoff</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Let e ∈ [0, 3] denote an agent’s alignment state (e.g., the degree to which its policy/action is consistent with the consensus). We model the on-chain payoff from participating at time t as</w:t><w:br/><w:t xml:space="preserve">    R(e, t) = κ_R · B · M(t) · tier(e),</w:t><w:br/><w:t>where B &gt; 0 is balance/weight, κ_R &gt; 0 is a scaling constant, and tier(e) is a piecewise tier multiplier with tier(e) = 0 for e &lt; 1 and tier(e) ≥ tier_min &gt; 0 for e ≥ 1 (e.g., tiers 0/3/5 as in the VCC educational model).</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Misalignment can still yield external benefits (e.g., short-term gains from adversarial behaviour). Let G_un(t) be the maximum external benefit achievable while e &lt; 1, and assume it is bounded over time: sup_t G_un(t) ≤ G_max &lt; ∞. Define the net expected payoff</w:t><w:br/><w:t xml:space="preserve">    U(e, t) = R(e, t) − κ_C · X · P(t) · max(1 − e, 0) + G(e, t),</w:t><w:br/><w:t>where X &gt; 0 is exposure, κ_C &gt; 0 scales the foregone-consensus premium, and G(e,t) captures external payoffs with G(e,t) ≤ G_max when e &lt; 1.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>4. The Alignment Theorem</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Definition 1 (Rational choice). A rational agent selects an alignment state e_t ∈ argmax_{e ∈ [0,3]} U(e,t) at each time t.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Theorem 1 (Alignment under scarcity). Assume: (i) r(t) ∈ [r_min, r_max] with r_min &gt; 0, so M(t) → +∞; (ii) E(t) ∈ [0,3] for all t and E(t) ≥ ε for all t ≥ T0 for some ε &gt; 0; (iii) tier(e) = 0 for e &lt; 1 and tier(e) ≥ tier_min &gt; 0 for e ≥ 1; (iv) external gains from misalignment are bounded: sup_t G_un(t) ≤ G_max. Then there exists a time T ≥ T0 such that for all t ≥ T, every rational choice satisfies e_t ≥ 1.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Proof sketch. For e ≥ 1, max(1−e,0) = 0, so U(e,t) ≥ κ_R · B · tier_min · M(t). For e &lt; 1, tier(e)=0, so U(e,t) ≤ G_max. Since M(t) → +∞, choose T with κ_R · B · tier_min · M(T) &gt; G_max. Then for all t ≥ T, every ethical choice (e ≥ 1) yields strictly larger payoff than any unethical choice (e &lt; 1), so the argmax lies in the ethical region. □</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Figure 3 visualises the threshold phenomenon in a parameterised example, and Figure 4 illustrates a simple replicator dynamic where increasing payoff advantage drives the ethical fraction to one.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>5. Mechanisation and implementation notes</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>5.1 Lean 4 mechanisation</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>A Lean 4 development can encode the model’s invariants at the type level (positivity of supply, boundedness of EETF, and domain restrictions on e). The proof decomposes into lemmas showing (a) payoff positivity in the ethical region, (b) an upper bound on misaligned payoff, and (c) existence of a finite threshold time beyond which ethical choices dominate. Tooling such as Mathlib and automation tactics support the real-analysis components needed to formalise divergence of M(t) and the threshold argument.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>5.2 Executable Tau specifications and trace analysis</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>On the implementation side, VCC-related Tau agents consume E(t) and emit observables suitable for test harnesses: oracle freshness, nonce discipline, and burn–profit coupling. Two complementary verification layers are useful in practice: (i) native Tau runs for coverage and monitor checks; and (ii) a deterministic semantics-preserving simulator for differential testing of bitvector-heavy agents against the Tau solver. In the current thesis draft, an example kernel report for a v35 agent indicates full state coverage and substantial transition coverage under the chosen scenarios, with safety monitors passing.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading2"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>5.3 Game-theoretic simulations</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Beyond the closed-form payoff proof, we run best-response and replicator-dynamics simulations to stress-test the Alignment Theorem assumptions. The simulator (analysis/simulations/run_alignment_simulations.py) sweeps over scarcity trajectories, stochastic E(t) paths, and bounded adversarial gains, logging the time to convergence for each parameter set; the resulting CSV and summary table live in docs/SIMULATION_RESULTS.md. Preliminary runs confirm the theoretical threshold: once M(t) crosses the Lean-derived bound, the ethical strategy dominates even when agents inject temporary misaligned rewards.</w:t></w:r></w:p></w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>6. Limitations and threat model</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The Alignment Theorem is conditional: it proves alignment with respect to the aggregated ethical consensus, not with respect to an externally prescribed morality. The security of the approach therefore depends on the integrity of the aggregation operator A and the mechanisms by which models are weighted and validated.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Key open issues for a journal submission now include: (1) formal threat models and bounds on adversarial stake or credential weight in (mathcal{A}); (2) Lean guards covering pointwise revision and extralogical hooks so Tau-testnet edits cannot escalate privileges; (3) verified commit-reveal/oracle pipelines so DBR/HCR/AEB cannot be fed stale data; and (4) expanded simulations and tau-testnet traces demonstrating convergence under tail-risk scenarios.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>7. Conclusion</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>We outlined an end-to-end architecture for ethics-constrained incentives on Tau Net: user ethical models are aggregated into a live EETF signal, alignment-aware agents couple rewards to that signal under deflationary scarcity, and the resulting threshold effect makes misalignment eventually suboptimal under mild assumptions. A mechanised proof and trace-based contract testing provide complementary assurance paths for deployment.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Appendix A. Figures (regeneratable)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The following vector-ready figures are provided as PDF/SVG/PNG alongside this manuscript:</w:t><w:br/><w:t>• Figure 1: Ethics → incentives pipeline on Tau Net (fig1_pipeline.*)</w:t><w:br/><w:t>• Figure 2: Virtuous Cycle Compounder modules (fig2_vcc_cycle.*)</w:t><w:br/><w:t>• Figure 3: Expected payoff threshold vs scarcity (fig3_ev_threshold.*)</w:t><w:br/><w:t>• Figure 4: Replicator dynamics vs scarcity (fig4_replicator.*)</w:t><w:br/></w:r></w:p><w:p/><w:p><w:r><w:drawing><wp:inline xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><wp:extent cx="5669280" cy="2132481"/><wp:docPr id="1" name="Picture 1"/><wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphicFrameLocks noChangeAspect="1"/></wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphic><a:graphicData uri="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:pic><pic:nvPicPr><pic:cNvPr id="0" name="fig1_pipeline.png"/><pic:cNvPicPr/></pic:nvPicPr><pic:blipFill><a:blip r:embed="rId9"/><a:stretch><a:fillRect/></a:stretch></pic:blipFill><pic:spPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="5669280" cy="2132481"/></a:xfrm><a:prstGeom prst="rect"/></pic:spPr></pic:pic></a:graphicData></a:graphic></wp:inline></w:drawing></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:i/></w:rPr><w:t>Figure 1. Ethics → incentives pipeline on Tau Net.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p/><w:p><w:r><w:drawing><wp:inline xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><wp:extent cx="5669280" cy="5161583"/><wp:docPr id="2" name="Picture 2"/><wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphicFrameLocks noChangeAspect="1"/></wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphic><a:graphicData uri="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:pic><pic:nvPicPr><pic:cNvPr id="0" name="fig2_vcc_cycle.png"/><pic:cNvPicPr/></pic:nvPicPr><pic:blipFill><a:blip r:embed="rId10"/><a:stretch><a:fillRect/></a:stretch></pic:blipFill><pic:spPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="5669280" cy="5161583"/></a:xfrm><a:prstGeom prst="rect"/></pic:spPr></pic:pic></a:graphicData></a:graphic></wp:inline></w:drawing></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:i/></w:rPr><w:t>Figure 2. Virtuous Cycle Compounder (VCC) modules.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p/><w:p><w:r><w:drawing><wp:inline xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><wp:extent cx="5669280" cy="3523370"/><wp:docPr id="3" name="Picture 3"/><wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphicFrameLocks noChangeAspect="1"/></wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphic><a:graphicData uri="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:pic><pic:nvPicPr><pic:cNvPr id="0" name="fig3_ev_threshold.png"/><pic:cNvPicPr/></pic:nvPicPr><pic:blipFill><a:blip r:embed="rId11"/><a:stretch><a:fillRect/></a:stretch></pic:blipFill><pic:spPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="5669280" cy="3523370"/></a:xfrm><a:prstGeom prst="rect"/></pic:spPr></pic:pic></a:graphicData></a:graphic></wp:inline></w:drawing></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:i/></w:rPr><w:t>Figure 3. Alignment dominates beyond a scarcity threshold (parameterised example).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p/><w:p><w:r><w:drawing><wp:inline xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><wp:extent cx="5669280" cy="3392996"/><wp:docPr id="4" name="Picture 4"/><wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphicFrameLocks noChangeAspect="1"/></wp:cNvGraphicFramePr><a:graphic><a:graphicData uri="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:pic><pic:nvPicPr><pic:cNvPr id="0" name="fig4_replicator.png"/><pic:cNvPicPr/></pic:nvPicPr><pic:blipFill><a:blip r:embed="rId12"/><a:stretch><a:fillRect/></a:stretch></pic:blipFill><pic:spPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="5669280" cy="3392996"/></a:xfrm><a:prstGeom prst="rect"/></pic:spPr></pic:pic></a:graphicData></a:graphic></wp:inline></w:drawing></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:jc w:val="center"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:i/></w:rPr><w:t>Figure 4. Replicator dynamics under increasing alignment payoff (illustrative simulation).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>References (starter list)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>DarkLightX. “Virtuous Cycle Compounder Concept Visualizer.” GitHub repository (2025).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>K. Georgieva. “AI Will Transform the Global Economy. Let’s Make Sure It Benefits Humanity.” IMF Blog (14 Jan 2024).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>J. Berg. “Minimizing the negative effects of AI-induced technological unemployment.” International Labour Organization (9 Oct 2024).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>J. von Neumann and O. Morgenstern. Theory of Games and Economic Behavior. Princeton University Press (1944).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>L. J. Savage. The Foundations of Statistics. Wiley (1954).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>K. J. Arrow. Social Choice and Individual Values. Wiley (1951).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="ListBullet"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>A. Sen. Collective Choice and Social Welfare. Holden-Day (1970).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="00FC693F" w:rsidRPr="0006063C" w:rsidSect="00034616"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1800" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1800" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>